graphic.is 2011-06-01

# Leading Source of Infographics, Photos, Videos, News and Features | Graphic.is

At Graphic.is, Inc. (“Graphic.is”) we appreciate your readership and support and place a high value on your personal privacy. We respect the personal nature of the information you provide us on our web site and staunchly recognize the importance of protecting this information. In adopting this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”), our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using your personal information with your reasonable expectations of privacy. This Privacy Policy may be revised at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our Privacy Policy.

#### When does Graphic.is collect my personal information?

You may provide personal information to Graphic.is in one of four ways: (1) by sharing your e-mail address when subscribing to our newsletter, (2) by sharing personal information when you post comments on our posts or stories, (3) by sharing contact information (Twitter username and Facebook account name) through our contests, or (4) by participating in a survey where an email address is requested. We may also ask for other information at other times but at no time will you be required to share any personal information to gain complete access to our site.

In addition to basic contact information, our analytics trackers may also collect information that is in no way personally identifiable. This may include the operating system you are working on, the Internet browser you are using, and the screen resolution of your computer.

#### How does Graphic.is use my personal information?

Depending on the portion of our site that you have subscribed to, we may use your information in a number of ways:

  * The email address you provided through our newsletter subscription form enables us to send you a daily digest of Graphic.is news stories. This subscription is entirely opt-in by the user. (We cannot subscribe you to the newsletter as you personally must have access to the email account in order to verify the subscription). Subscribers can opt-out of our newsletter at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link that is present on every email at the very bottom of the newsletter.
  * The email address associated with your account when you comment on our stories may be used in conjunction with contests and promotions hosted on Graphic.is’s website to notify you if you have won. Email addresses provided in comments are not used for any other reason.
  * If you choose to comment on Graphic.is stories through Disqus Comment system (Facebook Connect, Twitter, Yahoo and Open Id) we do not get access to your email address nor do we have any access to your personal data or private information.
  * We may at times request your participation in a survey. We will not provide your email addresses to any third party but may contact you via them to distribute prizes in associated giveaways.

#### Who else has access to my personal information?

The ads appearing on Graphic.is are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising serving partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. And, in the course of serving advertisements to this site, third party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to “opt-out”, please go to <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/privacy-policy.html>

We have also contracted with a number of advertising network partners to monitor certain pages of our website and RSS feeds for the purpose of reporting website and RSS traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, these advertising network partners may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to these network partners. For more information about how the information is collected and used, please see the following:

  * Buy Sell Ads’ privacy policy at [http://buysellads.com/about/privacy ](http://buysellads.com/about/privacy)
  * Commission Junction’s privacy policy at <http://www.cj.com/privacy_web_user.html>
  * Disqus privacy policy at <http://docs.disqus.com/help/30/>
  * Feedburner’s privacy policy at <http://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy>
  * Google’s privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/privacy.html ](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)
  * ValueClick Media’s privacy policy at <https://www.valueclickmedia.com/privacy.shtml>

#### Is there anything else I should know about my privacy and Graphic.is?

Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments pages or in any forums we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk. Privacy is a very personal matter and we encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://Graphic.is/terms-and-conditions/](http://graphic.is/terms-and-conditions/)

#### Your Consent

By using Graphic.is, you consent to our online privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at <http://graphic.is/contact/>
